Department of Mathematics fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Staff - faculty, 1971 - 1986; F-14-8; 27 cm of textual records
  - Faculty curricula vitae, 1971 - 1980; F-14-8-1; 17 cm of textual records
    - Faculty curriculum vitae - A to T, 1971; F-14-8-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-64)
    - Faculty curriculum vitae - A to L, 1972; F-14-8-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 14-64)
    - Faculty curriculum vitae - L to R, 1972; F-14-8-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 14-64)
    - Faculty curriculum vitae - S to V, 1972; F-14-8-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 14-64)
    - Faculty curriculum vitae - A to E, 1973; F-14-8-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 14-65)
    - Faculty curriculum vitae - F to K, 1973; F-14-8-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 14-65)
    - Faculty curriculum vitae - L to P, 1973; F-14-8-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 14-65)
    - Faculty curriculum vitae - R, 1973; F-14-8-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 14-65)
    - Faculty curriculum vitae - S, 1973; F-14-8-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 14-65)
    - Faculty curriculum vitae - T to Z, 1973; F-14-8-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 14-65)
    - Faculty curriculum vitae - A to Z, 1974; F-14-8-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 14-65)
    - Faculty curriculum vitae - A to F, 1980; F-14-8-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 14-65)
    - Faculty curriculum vitae - G to L, 1980; F-14-8-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 14-65)
    - Faculty curriculum vitae - M to R, 1980; F-14-8-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 14-65)
    - Faculty curriculum vitae - S to Z, 1980; F-14-8-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 14-65)
  - Miscellaneous, 1972 - 1986; F-14-8-2; 10 cm of textual records
    - External activities of faculty, 1977 - 1979; F-14-8-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-65)
    - Summer associates applications, 1972 - 1974; F-14-8-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 14-65)
    - Teaching assistant assignments, 1981 - 1986; F-14-8-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 14-66)
    - Teaching preferences, 1981 - 1983; F-14-8-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 14-66)
    - Teaching preferences #1, 1983 - 1984; F-14-8-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 14-66)
    - Teaching preferences #2, 1983 - 1984; F-14-8-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 14-66)
    - Teaching preferences #1, 1984 - 1985; F-14-8-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 14-66)
    - Teaching preferences #2, 1984 - 1985; F-14-8-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 14-66)
- Student Activities, 1981 - 1984; F-14-9; 1 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to departmental student activities. It includes minutes of meetings and related reports and memoranda.
  - Math Student Union, 1981 - 1984; F-14-9-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-66)
    Restricted in part
- Meetings, 1966 - 1988; F-14-10; 28 cm of textual records
  Series consists of minutes of meetings and related reports and memoranda.
  - Chair's meetings - faculty/university #1a, 1970 - 1974; F-14-10-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-66)
  - Chair's meetings - faculty/university #1b, 1974; F-14-10-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 14-66)
  - Chair's meetings - faculty/university #1c, 1970 - 1974; F-14-10-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 14-67)
  - Chair's meetings - faculty/university #2a, 1975; F-14-10-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 14-67)
  - Chair's meetings - faculty/university #2b, 1966 - 1975; F-14-10-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 14-67)
  - Chair's meetings - faculty/university #2c, 1975; F-14-10-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 14-67)
  - Chair's meetings - faculty/university #3a, 1975 - 1976; F-14-10-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 14-67)
  - Chair's meetings - faculty/university #3b, 1976 - 1977; F-14-10-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 14-67)
  - Chair's meetings - faculty/university #3c, 1975 - 1977; F-14-10-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 14-67)
  - Chair's meeting with the President, 1981 - 1986; F-14-10-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 14-67)
  - Chair's meeting with the Dean of Science #1a, 1985 - 1988; F-14-10-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 14-68)
  - Chair's meeting with the Dean of Science #1b, 1984 - 1985; F-14-10-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 14-68)
  - Chair's meeting with the Dean of Science #1c, 1983 - 1984; F-14-10-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 14-68)
  - Chair's meeting with the Dean of Science #2a, 1983; F-14-10-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 14-68)
  - Chair's meeting with the Dean of Science #2b, 1982 - 1983; F-14-10-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 14-68)
  - Chair's meeting with the Dean of Science #2c, 1982; F-14-10-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 14-68)
  - Chair's meeting with the Dean of Science #2d, 1982; F-14-10-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 14-68)